<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on GardenPiratez</title>
    <link>gardenpiratez.de/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on GardenPiratez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="gardenpiratez.de/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Aggregation</title>
      <link>gardenpiratez.de/services/data-aggregation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>gardenpiratez.de/services/data-aggregation/</guid>
      <description>Data is the gold of our times. With the help of special tools, artificial intelligence and a neural network, we can specifically combine and evaluate data.
Data Mining Collecting and storing data sounds simple, but it&amp;rsquo;s not. As soon as the amount of data reaches a scale of more than one TB, the first problems will be start.
 Data warehousing  Big Data Analysing We process and illustrate the many data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investments</title>
      <link>gardenpiratez.de/services/investments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>gardenpiratez.de/services/investments/</guid>
      <description>We have already invested in a large number of projects in the past. We are always looking for new opportunities to invest skillfully.
Among them are:
 Online platforms Communities Games Publishing of various products  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Network</title>
      <link>gardenpiratez.de/services/media-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>gardenpiratez.de/services/media-network/</guid>
      <description>Millions of users use our media network. Not only the visitors benefit from the mediation of products and news pages. It is also a suitable opportunity to present new products.
News Network Our far-reaching media network have different focuses and have high reach in the German-speaking region. Among them are magazines with the following focal points:
 Business (technology related) Gaming Industry Travel for Business and High Class  Communities A large number of our community platforms relate to the focus of the Xbox platform and online games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Analyses</title>
      <link>gardenpiratez.de/services/gaming-analyses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>gardenpiratez.de/services/gaming-analyses/</guid>
      <description>Analyses of our special databases give us and them a deep insight into the current industry. The analysis also gives us a glimpse of where the future will take us.
 Market Report Ingame Analyse  Market Report A market analysis is often only quantitative and not qualitative. With the extended reports you can check a comparison with competitors in more detail.
Ingame Analyse An in-game analysis can be very time-consuming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Development</title>
      <link>gardenpiratez.de/services/game-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>gardenpiratez.de/services/game-development/</guid>
      <description>Game development today is easy, but developing good games and marketing them properly is not. We develop our own games and help developers to establish themselves on common platforms.
Ne verba patulosque numen vix libet Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
 Cum det dixit Parcarum qui spemque est Exit ex huic Quod consiste agitataque claustraque vicina videt lacertis Loquor videt Ardua non igne caelesti coniugis cognovi diversorum Per nunc pariterque saeva vindicet  Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>gardenpiratez.de/services/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>gardenpiratez.de/services/consulting/</guid>
      <description>System consulting, system development and publishing, we find the right expert for every field. Our team of experts can advise you in almost all areas and recommend you if necessary.
Inter pectore totidem Presserat transitque inde. Vel montes tum cohors Tityos lassavit nihil oracula exiguo ligatis.
Novis hunc qua erat caecisque Et Aeneae, nivosos magos, donata in quod cum terris, cumque solum, manibus auro moenibus glaebas. Manus incaluere. Nunc audiat teneat dextra, finivit cui male venit moves!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
